

MOHAMED ERZIKI

UNITY DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Unity Developer with over 4+ years of experience in writing clean code. I was built games and apps VR also AR, skills including Innovation, interaction, 3D, motion, visual, and prototyping work. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. I have a passion to learn everything new in the industry of games and VR/AR.

CONTACT

Address:

BenGuerir City, Morocco

Phone:

+ 212644215984

Email:

mderziki@gmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/mohamederziki

HOBBIES





Music

Swimming



O^{*}
Photography

EXPERIENCE

UNITY VR DEVELOPER : VEEZEN - INTERNSHIP

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022 Build Voice Bot for medical health application with

virtual reality and arti cial intelligence.

EON REALITY: THEORETICAL AND PRACTICAL TRAINING

Oct 2021 - Apr 2022

Modeling, Texturing, Rigging, and Animation of the assets for AR and VR applications, Interactive application development basic and advance.

UNITY AR DEVELOPER - FREELANCE

Apr 2022 - Present

I built this project application AR for education to teach kids alphabet English with interactive objects.

— UNITY VR DEVELOPER

Mar 2022 - May 2022

I built the application Fire ghting's VR to train employees in many scenarios and avoid many

accidents in real life.

UNITY GAME DEVELOPER - FREELANCE

May 2018 - Present

Build indie and hyper-casual games 3d for clients develop games from sketch to design levels and scripting.

EDUCATION

MAKING YOUR FIRST VIRTUAL REALITY GAME University of London, Coursera

 BUILDING INTERACTIVE3D CHARACTERS AND SOCIAL VR University of London, Coursera

 3D INTERACTION DESIGN IN VIRTUAL REALITY University of London, Coursera

3D MODELS FOR VIRTUAL REALITY
 University of London, Coursera

— INTRODUCTION TO VIRTUAL REALITY University of London, Coursera

— AUGMENTED REALITY & VIRTUAL REALITY Moroccan Digital University, UM6P

AUGMENTED REALITY & VIRTUAL REALITY LEVEL
 Mohammed VI Polytechnic University, BenGuerir

 SCIENTIFIC STEM HIGH SCHOOL Essalam High School, BenGuerir

SKILLS

- PROGRAMMING LANGUAGESC#, Kotlin, Java, XCode, Python, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL Programming, JSON, .NET, XML.
- GRAPHICS: Shaders, URP, HDRP, SRP, 3D Math, Linear Algebra, Visual e ects, Normal Mapping, Particle systems.
- IDES: Visual Studio, Eclipse, Android Studio, Mono Develop
- VERSION CONTROL :Unity Collaborate, Git, Perforce.
- SOFTWARE/TOOLS: Unity3D, 3Ds Max, Maya, Blender, Vuforia, AR Core, AR Kit, Unity Bundle, Unity assets, SQL, Android Studio.